情r怎N  基D?
How you doing   Keaton?
我的p腿失去了知X…
I can't feel my legs...
P
Keyser
浜昧?
Ready?
F在是什Nr候了?
What time is it?
12:30
一切得牧星期前的~sf起
It all started back in New York six weeks ago.
一vMd械部件的卡 在皇后^外被劫持了
A truck loaded with stripped gun parts got jacked outside of Queens.
那司C]目睹劫持者的相貌
The driver didn't see anyone   but someone fucked up.
只到Ψ秸f的一句 有r候@些索就蛄
He heard a voice. Sometimes that's all you need.
-克R{斯先生? -天!就他不能我睡安X?
- Mr.McManus? - Christ! Don't you fucking guys ever sleep?
-我被授⒛憔辛 -去死吧  i
- We have a warrant for your arrest. - Fuck you   pig.
陶德霍克尼?
Todd Hockney?
-是l找我? -我是~s市警局的
- Who wants to know? - New York Police Department.
-死的 -不S!
- Shit. - Freeze!
e!
Hold it!
你真是如R大
Sure you brought enough guys?
@很:
It's quite simple:
餐d的食物更Q口味   而毫不适其整w的g感
A restaurant that changes with the taste without losing the overall aesthetic.
Q而言之…
In other words...
…夥K不是由bI造的
...the atmosphere will not be painted on the walls.
-我e例碚f-- -@得我自己砼
- Let me give you an example-- - This I had to see for myself.
David
-我在公事 -有e的公事等你去
- I'm in a meeting. - Time for another one.
我斫榻B一下  @位是大l奎恩
Everyone   this is David Kujan.
美海P特e探T奎恩
Special Agent Kujan. US Customs.
@孜皇羌~s市警局的
These gentlemen are from the New York Police Department.
你馍不e  比我想像的要好
You look good. Better than I would have thought.
不^是P於\被劫的小麻
A small matter of a stolen truck loaded with guns.
基D 先生?
Mr.Keaton?
原  我要失陪一下
Will you excuse us for a moment?
我得你回局e去   事情不是三删渚驼f的清的
We have some questions to ask you downtown. You'll be a while.
不  不.坐下
No. Please   sit down.
不^是些小事
This is a small problem.
慢用.我t些再
Enjoy the meal. I'll talk to you later.
我根本]理由出F在那e
It didn't make sense that I'd be there.
@些砘锉臼贺M盈的江洋大I
These guys were hard-core hijackers...
…而我s也被列在其中
...but there I was.
不^我rK不害怕
At that point   I wasn't scared.
我清楚自己是清白的   他也不能拿我怎N
I knew I hadn't done anything they could do me for.
此外  @^程很有趣
Besides   it was fun.
我得把自己也成 是名狼藉的罪犯
I got to make like I was notorious.
你都知道程式
You all know the drill.
被叫到的人就上前一步   念出上的
When your number is called   step forward and repeat the phrase you've been given.
一  上前
Number 1   step forward.
"把匙o我  混蛋"
"Hand me the keys you fucking cocksucker."
二  上前
Number 2   step forward.
"把他匙o我  你@死的混蛋!"
Gimme the fuckin' keys   you fuckin' cocksucker motherfucker!
停  退後.三上前
Knock it off. Get back. Number 3   step forward.
-"把匙o我  混蛋" -v英Z
- "Hand me the keys   you cocksucker." - In English   please.
-你f什N? -v英Z
- Excuse me? - In English.
"把匙o我  混蛋" @哪翰α?
Hand me the fuckin' keys   you cocksucker. What the fuck?
四上前
Number 4   step forward.
@根本是胡  全都是栽E嫁
It was bullshit. The whole rap was a setup.
"把匙o我  混蛋"
"Hand me the keys you fucking cocksucker."
全是l子的e
It was the cops' fault.
象@拥娜烁本不P在一起
You don't put guys like that into a room together.
l知道l生些什N?
Who knows what can happen?
"把匙o我  混蛋"
"Hand me the keys you fucking cocksucker."
@事情一定你很^痛
This has really got to be embarrassing for you guys.
他了我整晚上
They drilled us all night.
\被劫  有人暴跳如雷   而l子s束手o策
Someone was mad about that truck hijacking and the cops had nothing.
所以希望有人撞到他口上
They were hoping somebody would slip up and give them something.
他清楚我不能反抗   他知道怎N向我施加毫
They knew we wouldn't fight   they knew how to lean on us.
他一直就是如此   我的嗬早被`踏的o行
They've been doing it forever. Our rights went out the window.
那直就是可u的C^人
It was a violation. Disgraceful.
他最先的是克R{斯   他是打家劫舍的老手
They went after McManus first. Topnotch entry man.
什N卡?
What truck?
-\的卡  sN -"sN"?
- The truck with the guns   fucko. - "Fucko"?
他是好人  只是有r有c狂
He was a good guy. Crazy   though.
想知道你的好兄弟范斯特是怎Nf的?
Wanna know what your pal Fenster told us?
-fl? -克R{斯
- Say who? - McManus.
他f的完全是另外一情r
He told us another story.
是f那得了痢疾的妓女?
Is that the one about the hooker with the dysentery?
范斯特是和克R{斯一起   是油腔滑{的砘
Fenster always worked with McManus. He was a real tight-ass.
但是f到正事上   他_算是明人
But when it came to the job   he was right on. A smart man.
-你f什N? -我f他教你的
- What are you saying? - I said he'll flip you.
-他什N? -教你.狠狠的教你
- He'll what? - Flip you. Flip you for real.
-我怕O了  ^m -好吧
- I'm shaking. Come on. - Okay.
-回答我的} -後面那位也的清?
- Answer my questions. - Can you hear me in the back?
喂?
Hello?
我要律
I want my lawyer.
我要你@些死的l子G掉碗
I'm gonna have your fuckin' badge   cocksucker.
陶德霍克尼:爆破＜
Todd Hockney: good with explosives.
毫o疑  @砘锊出u任何人
Without a doubt   the one guy who didn't give a fuck about anybody.
你根本]有立根
You guys don't have a fuckin' leg to stand on.
你以槭?
You think so   tough guy?
我能以在皇后^T劫的罪名起V你
I can put you in Queens during the hijacking.
是?
Really?
我就住在皇后^
I live in Queens.
所以你就@N把事情 在一起告我  垡蛩继?
Did you put that together yourself   Einstein?
你的那群猴子手下就是@Nk事的?
You got a team of monkeys working full time on this?
知道你若是再投胎  怎?
You know what happens if you do another turn in the joint?
我狂帜憷习
I fuck your father in the shower   and have a snack.
-你想告我?白V -我Sr控告你
- Are you gonna charge me   dickhead? - I'll charge you when I'm ready.
-{什N砀嫖? -你自己心e很清楚
- With what? - You know damn well   dead man.
基D?
But Keaton?
基D是他重c的目
Keaton was the real prize for them for obvious reasons.
犯e的是你  而不是我
It was your mistake   not mine.
你到底完了]有?
Did you ever stop to ask me?
我行不改姓  坐不改名
I've been walking around with the same face   the same name.
是正商人
I'm a businessman.
做什N生意?餐d生意?
What's that? The restaurant business?
F在你要做的就是o我老招供
No. From now on you're in the "getting fucked by us" business.
我把你K之以法的  混蛋
I'm gonna make you famous   cocksucker.
我已f了…
Like I said...
…犯e的是你
...it was your mistake
…而不是我
...not mine.
你要是胡y控V我
You charge me with this shit...
…我一定反V你
...and I'll beat it.
明白?
Okay?
^mf卡的事吧  屁精
Let's get back to the truck   asshole.
真有人管管@事
Really   somebody's got to do something about this shit.
他硬泳驼椅衣   我真是受蛄
They put me in holding every five minutes. So I did a little time.
y道f每Gv卡 就都得把我PM?
Does that mean I get railed every time a truck finds it's way gone?
他去死吧
Fuck 'em.
斯特  放c好?
Fenster   will you relax?
-他根本]有任何C -你f的  o{o
- These guys don't have any probable cause. - You fuckin' right. No PC.
真他f的太α 只要曾犯^小e  他就揪住你不放
You're goddamn right. You do some time   never let you go.
他我是罪犯般看待
They treat me like a criminal.
-那N我t早也成罪犯 -你本砭褪亲锓
- I'll end up a criminal. - You are a criminal.
致镎f的那N直接?
Why'd you got to go and do that?
-我只是在做假O -做你的假O去吧
- I'm trying to make a point. - Why don't you make your point?
你我┩噶
You're making me tired all over.
去死吧
Fuck it then.
-我f你已死了 -是?
- I heard you were dead. - Yeah?
-你]有e -我f的是你已收手不至
- You heard right. - Word I got is you hung up your spurs.
-@是怎N回事? -究竟怎Nf的?
- What's that all about? - What's this?
{言f基D已改^自新 和伊迪菲娜琳打的火
Rumor has it Keaton's gone straight. I hear he's tapping Edie Finneran.
那是l?
Who's that?
她是重量的刑事qo律
She's a heavyweight criminal lawyer from uptown.
她成了基D的票
I hear she's Keaton's meal ticket.
是  基D?
How 'bout it   Keaton?
你有律的R子?
You a lawyer's wife?
你是怎N勾上她的?
What kind of retainer you giving her?
兔  叫他收吧
Do your friend a favor...tell him to keep quiet.
迪恩基D…
Dean Keaton...
改^自新?
Gone clean?
我X得不可能
Say it ain't so.
-是f卡就是你的? -克  算了吧
- Or was it you that hit that truck? - Mac   forget him.
你和律^]有?
Did you get to talk to your lawyer?
整妒虑椴贿^是藉口
This whole thing was a shakedown.
-槭颤N@Nf? -你被指J^状?
- What makes you say that? - How many times you been in a lineup?
通常是你和四不相干的人
It's always you and four dummies.
警方找些流浪h   每次o他十K
The PD are paying homeless guys $10 a head half the time.
他不同r把五罪犯放在一起
There's no way they'd line five felons in the same row.
-那音指J呢? -那o非是形式
What's a voice lineup? Public defender could get you out of that.
-槭颤N要找上我? -是邦{查局的砘
- Why the hell was I strip searched? - It was the feds.
有v\被截下了
A truckload of guns gets snagged.
海P的人到~s警局要答案 於是他碚椅的麻
Customs comes down on NYPD for answers. They come up with us.
-他把我成救命稻草 -我就@N被他玩
- They're clutching at straws. - I had a guy's finger up my ass.
F在是星期五了?
Is it Friday already?
是的  花花公子
Yeah   lover boy.
想被人修理? 戆  我好好疼你的
You want a piece? Jump in. I'll love you.
那N究竟是他哪人渣的?
So who in the goddamn piss hell stole our fucking truck?
-你f什N? -是l偷了那?
- What did you say? - Who stole the fucking truck?
-我不想知道 -]人你  正人
- I don't want to know. - Who asked you   workingman?
做@事的人去死吧 我F在想知道那跛子是什N人?
Fuck who did it. What I want to know is   who's the gimp?
-]他的事 -全是你在f  我怎N知道?
- He's okay. - Says you. How do I know that?
怎N  拐_佬? ff你的故事吧
What about it   pretzel man? What's your story?
他叫"口水先生"
His name is Verbal.
S伯肯特
Verbal Kint.
-"口水先生"? -
- Verbal? - Yeah.
真名是_  人人f我太多
Roger   really. People say I talk too much.
我正想叫你]嘴
I was going to tell you to shut up.
-我以前^一二次 -是在州局.我因樵p_罪被逮M了局子
- We met before   once or twice. - In County. I was in for fraud.
我曾一同被指J 後砣绾瘟?
You were in a lineup then   too. What happened?
被判了90天  刑放
I walked. 90 days   suspended.
-你也不是好人 -好了  大家我f…
- So you did it. - All right   now look...
…我都因@事被M
...we've all been put out by this whole thing   right?
我想我O法挽回c面子
I figure we owe it to ourselves to salvage a little dignity.
我和斯特f有渡意
Now   me and Fenster heard about a little job.
安o汉?
Why don't you just calm down?
他ff又怎N了?
What do you care what he has to say?
我不^S便ff
I'm just talking here.
看砉肯尼先生 似乎想我要f什N…
It seems to me like Mr.Hockney wants to hear it...
…而我知道斯特亦有d趣
...and I know Fenster's down.
你呢?夥
What about you   guy?
然有d趣
I'm interested.
看到]?
There. See?
我只想行使我的自由集
I'd like to exercise my right to free assembly.
]鹤觳恍?
Why don't you just shut up?
你是不明白
You're missing the point.
不
No.
不明白的人是你
You're missing the point.
我不想你f任何事
I don't want to hear anything from you.
我δ愕纳意]d趣
I don't care about your job.
此外…
And...
…我不想和你有任何P
...I want nothing to do with any of you.
我很抱歉@Nf   但你全都鬼去吧
I beg your pardon   but you can all go to hell.
迪恩基D…
Dean Keaton...
…想正做人
...gone the high road.
@世界是怎N了?
What is the world coming to?
去他的
Fuck him.
事情就是@N_始的:
And that was how it started:
我五因槟有的罪名
Five of us brought in on a trumped-up charge...
…被@些低能宏P了M
...to be leaned on by half-wits.
在@何艺娌荒芏嗾f
I really can't talk about it much here.
T警永h也想不到的是…
What the cops never figured out   and what I know now...
…@些人永h不屈服
...was that these men would never break   never lie down.
永h不屈服於任何人
Never bend over for anybody.
任何人都不行
Anybody.
-你是l? -FBI探T芸税
- Who are you? - Agent Jack Baer   FBI.
-死了多少人? -迄今橹拱lF15具企w
- How many dead? - 15 so far.
在^m打扑下的企w
They're still pulling bodies out of the water.
-有生者? -有
- Any survivors? - Two.
一被送M了州立t院   但他正在昏迷中
One guy's in County hospital   but he's in a coma.
地方z察官ё吡肆硪砘   一跛_的~s人
The DA has a second guy   a cripple from New York.
上^下令封iF
The chief wants this place sealed off.
要是有e的}   就o他吧
If you have any questions   give him a call.
我是奎恩  我去了洛杉   星期二才回
This is Dave Kujan. I'll be in Los Angeles until Tuesday.
若有急事  可M }佩德_警署的芊蚶e…
If you need to reach me   contact Jeff Rabin of the San Pedro Police Department...
…找染112就可  祝你利
...at extension 112. Have a nice day.
-我槭颤N不能他? -我已f了…
- Why can't I see him? - I told you...
…地方z察官昨晚磉@e
...the DA came down here last night ready to arraign...
…涞人到了就_始提
...even before they moved him to County.
然後^了五分   肯特的律露面了…
Kint's lawyer shows up five minutes later...
…地方z察官出 的r候像是蔫了的茄子
...the DA comes out looking like the bogeyman smacked him around.
他o他了口供   Kc他_成fh
They take his statement   and they cut him a deal.
-他以什N砥鹪V他? -非法持械  是p罪
- Did they charge him with anything? - Weapons   misdemeanor 2.
究竟是怎N回事?
What is that?
@旱氖挛镆呀 全移交o地方z察官  明白?
I give the DA credit for getting that much   you understand?
一下
Excuse me   sir.
整妒虑殚_始有政治色彩 市L昨晚磉^了
This whole thing has turned political. The mayor was here last night.
今天早上州L也曾打o^
The chief. This morning   the governor called   okay?
我告V你  @砘锏尼崤_很硬
I'm telling you   this guy is protected from up on high by the Prince of Darkness.
-得我f的吧 -他什Nr候可保外出?
- Take my word for it. - When does he post bail?
-可能最多再^尚r -我想要他
- Maybe two hours   tops. - I want to see him.
-不行 -我一定得他
- No. - I gotta see him.
-不  不行-- -你得臀
- No. I can't-- - You gotta do this for me.
我大老h砭褪榱诉@事
I came a long way for this.
M
Dave   please.
就算我你他   他也什N都不f的
Even if I let you talk to him   he won't talk to you.
他X得是在被
He's paranoid about being recorded.
-他知道室eM布CP -我戒了
- He knows the rooms are wired. - I quit.
我不是他  只不^S便T了
This won't be an interrogation   just a friendly chat.
-他不M室的 -那就去e的地方
- He won't go into the interrogation room. - Then someplace else.
哪e呢?
Where?
不行  不行
No   no.
若@是毒品交易  那毒品呢? 如果是\  那又是l指使的?
If this was a dope deal   where's the dope? If it was a hit   who called it?
我相信@些} 在你心e已有了答案
I'm sure you have a host of wild theories to answer all these questions.
-你很清楚我的想法 -@直狂O了  而且也]什N意x
- You know what I think. - That's crazy   and it doesn't even matter.
@砘锔本不知情 他的背景也已查出砹
The guy's got total immunity. His story checks out.
-他]有你想知道的答案 -我知道他]有答案
- He doesn't know what you want to know. - I don't think he does   not exactly.
但事情]有那N  相信我
But there's a lot more to his story   believe me.
我想知道a^上那二十七人的死因
I wanna know why 27 men died on that pier...
@事c九千一百f毒品有P 但F鼍拐也坏蕉酒
...for what looks to be $91 million worth of dope that wasn't there.
此外  我想_J迪恩基D的死
And above all   I want to be sure Dean Keaton's dead.
他_死了
He's dead.
就o我尚r吧  到他被保就Y束
Come on. Two hours. Just till he makes bail.
他都死了
They're all dead.
我才不在乎你f的 @基D有多害…
I don't care how tough you say Keaton was...
…船上]有生的人
...nobody on that boat could've come out alive.
-他能f? -他醒磉不到一小r
- Is he talking? - He regained consciousness an hour ago.
f了些  但不是英Z 然後就停下了
He spoke   not English   then he lapsed.
-是匈牙利? -我不知道  也S是吧
- Hungarian? - That might have been it.
-他大部分是匈牙利人 -你得把@穿上
- Most of them were Hungarians. - You gotta put this on.
病人很容易感染病菌
Burn victims are very susceptible to infection.
有  那菏墙的
And   of course   there's no smoking.
戴上口罩  有e去碰他
Keep your mask up. Please don't touch him.
他死?
Is he gonna die?
他全身有六成被 肋骨嗔--
He's burned 60 percent of his body   broken ribs--
叫t院保安.人守在T口
Call security. Put a man on the door.
-他有危U? -
- Is he dangerous? - Yes.
去吧
Do it.
快去
Do it now.
s耳?我是拜 穆迳即o你打淼
Joel? Baer. Down at LA County.
他在a^找到的那人 叫阿科西卡瓦什
Look   the guy they pulled out of the harbor is Arkosh Kovash.
是的  我明白
Yes   I'm sure.
不  他受了重
No   he's all fucked up.
我不清
I can't hear you.
]鹤旌?我在打
Will you shut up? I'm on the phone.
Yes.
不  直至我派人砜粗他
No   not till I put a man on him.
派f匈牙利Z的人
Send me someone who can speak Hungarian.
他已醒了 @砘镎f就象泰妓女
He's awake. He's talking like a Thai hooker.
P W
Keyser Soze.
-什N? -P少W!
- What? - Keyser Soze!
@是怎N了?
No shit?
到法院去找丹曼厮固
Call Dan Metzheiser over at Justice...
…有海P的大l奎恩
...and find Dave Kujan from Customs.
S伯  @是海P的奎恩探T
Verbal   this is Agent Kujan from Customs.
幸
Nice to meet you.
他想在你x_前}
He wants to ask you a few questions before you go.
-什N}? -大部分是P於迪恩基D的
- What about? - About a Dean Keaton   mostly.
但我想先由在~s的指J起
I'd like to start at the lineup back in New York.
-我能喝杯咖啡? -稍後再f吧  先ff指Jr的事
- Can I get some coffee? - In a while. Let's talk about the lineup.
我真的很口渴 我就象小孩子般的容易水
I'm really thirsty. I used to dehydrate as a kid.
有次我尿出的小便就象鼻涕一
Once I got so bad my piss come out like snot.
-就是那N又庥终车-- -我去o你搞咖啡
- It was all thick and gooey-- - I'll get your fucking coffee.
便臀乙_一杯
Get me one   too   while you're at it.
那砘锾o了
That guy is tense.
o足以使人致命
Tension is a killer.
我曾加入^在伊利Z州邵崎市 的一男四重唱M合
I used to be in a barbershop quartet in Skokie   Illinois.
男中音就叫基普迪斯金   是超大胖子
The baritone was this guy named Kip Diskin   big fat guy.
他每天早上都o的要命--
Like   orca fat. He was so stressed in the morning--
-我F在是想湍 -xx  我很感激
- You know we're trying to help you. - Sure   and I appreciate that.
我也想湍  奎恩探T 我喜gT警
And I wanna help you   Agent Kujan. I like cops.
我曾粝氤槁邦探T   可是我的--
I would've liked to have been a fed   but my CP--
你]ξf 我知道你清楚一切
You're not tellin' us everything. I know you know something.
我已Φ胤z察官全交待了
I told the DA everything I know.
我知道你喜g基D
I know you like Keaton.
-我明白你J樗是好人 -我知道他很好
- I know you think he's a good man. - I know he was good.
他曾是污的T警
He was a corrupt cop.
15年前的事了  他是好\
Sure. 15 years ago   but he was a good thief.
T警不他的行楹戏化
The cops wouldn't let him go legit.
迪恩基D是垃圾
Dean Keaton was a piece of shit.
你想奈疑砩系玫近c什N?
Are you trying to get a rise out of me?
-我只想你的故事 -已全f了
- I just wanna hear your story. - It's all there.
能抽支?
May I have a cigarette?
-根你的口供-- -o火
- According to your statement-- - I need a light.
根你的口供   你只是小毛\…
According to your statement   you're a short-con operator...
…不入流的--
...run-of-the-mill--
根你的口供   你只是小毛\…
According to your statement   you're a short-con operator...
…不入流的_子
...run-of-the-mill scams.
@些口供已被封存了
It's been suppressed. Anything in there is inadmissible.
我知道  你做了逗媒灰 你已被完全豁免
I know. Sweet deal you have here. Total immunity.
我因非法持罪被起V 有六月的日子得熬
I do have the weapons charge. I'm lookin' at six whole months hard time.
JR一叫比迪莫的商人?
You know a dealer named Ruby Deemer?
JR一叫s翰保_的教徒?
You know a religious guy named John Paul?
-知道阿提卡的比? -我和他]什N瓜葛
- You know Ruby's in Attica? - He didn't have my lawyer.
我JR比  他很受人尊敬
I know Ruby. He's big on respect.
他是我的好朋友  也很喜g我
He's a good friend of mine   likes me very much.
我知你的C供已被封存 可比交[V
I know your testimony is sealed. Ruby's well connected.
有S多朋友樗效力
He's got lots of friends inside who do favors for him.
若他知你把他的名字供o了 地方z察官  知道他怎N做?
What would he say if he found out you dropped his name to the DA?
-上面根本]提比的事 -可我@Nλf
- There's nothing there on Ruby. - I'll be sure to mention that to him.
知道我倪@行W了什N? 就是如何J出词
Know what I've learned on the job? How to spot a murderer.
假O捉了宗\案的三疑犯
Say you arrest three guys for the same killing.
你把他P通宵
Put them in jail overnight.
到了第二天早上   l要是睡著了  l就是词
Next morning   whoever's sleeping is your man.
如果你犯了罪  等到被捕 你的戒心就懈了
If you're guilty   you know you're caught. You let your guard down.
-明白? -不
- You follow me? - No.
我_T山的直f
Let me get to the point.
我比你明   我查出我要知的事
I'm smarter than you   and I'm gonna find out what I wanna know.
o你是否喜g  我都查出真相
I'll get it   whether you like it or not.
我也不是鼠
I'm not a rat.
xx
Thanks.
我曾在瓜地R拉L^ 咖啡豆磨的新r咖啡
When I was pickin' beans in Guatemala we used to make fresh coffee.
直接渖险下的那N  好喝O了
Right off the trees   I mean. That was good.
-@味道糟透了  l我是在警察局e呢 -能^m?
- This is shit   but I'm in a police station. - Can we get started again?
指JY束後怎恿?
What happened after the lineup?
那值班的ξ艺f不能保你
The desk sergeant was telling me he couldn't release you.
你能相信?你甚至未被起V
Can you believe that? You weren't even charged.
死的T警
Damn police.
我要o你的拍照
I wanna have pictures taken of your face.
-明天就送到地方z察官那 -算了吧
- I'll take them to the DA tomorrow. - Forget about it.
星期一我就把@事蟮酱笈F去
I'll have this thing in front of a grand jury by Monday.
我不想再@事了
I don't want to talk about it   okay?
弗提和雷Z那怎Nf?
What did Fortier and Renault say?
他需要多些rg考]投Y
They asked for more time to think about investing.
死的
Damn it.
需要多些rg质颤N?
More time for what?
o你怎N掩我的v史 他是查到我的底
No matter how you cover my tracks they're still gonna find out about me.
相信我
Give me some credit.
我湍愠吻宓   我一起去庭群献h
I got you this far. Let's go to the grand jury.
-如果不@  @事不停-- -@事永h不停
- This isn't gonna stop if we don't-- - It's never going to stop   period.
下星期所有投Y者都㈦x我
By next week   every investor in the city is gonna be walking away from us.
完了
It's finished.
我氐淄炅
I'm finished.
ep言放  基D
Don't give up on me now.
@事永h也不停
It's never gonna stop.
我勰
I love you.
他今晚Я宋
They ruined me in there tonight.
我勰
I love you.
你到了?
Do you hear me?
什N?
What?
好了
All right.
去我家吧
Let's just go to my place.
明天再想@些┦
We'll worry about this tomorrow.
走吧
Let's go.
范斯特和克R{斯 有很好的:
Fenster and McManus had a cagey proposition:
X淼目  LU高  利也大
A fast-jump   high-risk   long money.
我都知道那行得通
We all knew it could be done.
我想那事若是k牧司偷⑷
The way I figured   to do it wrong meant killing.
可要k好就要集R五人
To do it right took five men.
五人的PI就是基D
Five men meant Keaton.
基D是令人信服的
Keaton took convincing.
~sT警出租公司
New York's finest taxi service.
胡f
Bullshit.
他早就已不至
They don't operate anymore.
克R{斯有朋友在十四^ 他星期四收到了L
McManus has a friend in the 14th precinct. They're coming out for one job   Thursday.
他涫帐耙 哪戏亲咚石的砘
They're pickin' up a guy smuggling emeralds from South America.
克R{斯已找到了NE人
McManus already has a fence set up.
-NE人?是l? -是加州人  叫雷德福特
- A fence? Who? - Some guy in California called Redfoot.
-我奈绰f^@砘 -你一定要
- I never heard of him. - You have to come.
-我砼c不  c你何干? -他不JR我  只JR你
- What's it to you whether I do it or not? - They don't know me. You do.
除非你一起  否t他不信我
They won't take me unless you go.
替我想想  我需要@PX
Look at me. I need this.
y道你就不需要?@是你家?
You're telling me you don't need this? Is this your place?
我不是在打裟 y道你就打算跟著@律吃?
I'm not knocking you. You got a good scam going with this lawyer.
Σ黄
Sorry.
算了
It's okay.
你f得不e
You say it's the real thing? That's cool.
你]事吧?
You okay?
我已洗手不
I was out of line.
可他仍不放^我 你很明白@c
But they're never gonna stop with us. You know that.
即使象你般清白  他仍p著你
As clean as you get   they'll never let you go now.
@N  既能ol子色看   同r我也得了好
This way   we hit the cops where it hurts   and we get well in the meantime.
你真的]事?
You sure you're okay?
]事的
I'll be all right.
你看…
Look   I...
-…我有r候-- -ef了
- ...sometimes get-- - Forget it.
我今晚可能a血
I'll probably shit blood tonight.
那N…
So...
…他想怎N下手?
...how do they wanna do it?
克R{斯想_⒔ 可我反
McManus wants to go in shooting. I say no.
斯特呢?哈肯尼呢?
Fenster? Hockney?
他都豁出去了  什N都值某
They're pretty pissed off. They'll do anything.
我有l不用⑷魏稳说穆
I got a way to do it without killing anyone.
可就象我f的   ]有你  他不我加入
But like I say   they won't let me in without you.
三百f?
$3 million?
也S更多
Maybe more.
不⑷
No killing.
只要依我的方法行事便成
Not if we do it my way.
~sT警程公司是地下Q呼
New York's finest taxi service was not your normal taxi service.
那是~s污T警的生工具…
It was a ring of corrupt cops in the NYPD that ran a high-profit racket...
…他接d走私客和毒
...driving smugglers and drug dealers all over the city.
付上每公里三百元的rX   你就有了私人的{白T警l
For $300 a mile   you got your own blue and white...
他甚至溆忻片
...and a police escort. They even had their own business cards.
]^多久  有人提出了| 而@程服找喔娼KY
After a while   somebody started asking questions   and the taxi service shut down.
S後日部的人 ⑸姘傅娜硕季胁读
Ever since then   Internal Affairs has been waiting to catch them in the act.
我就δ氢啡讼率
That's where we came in.
-旅程愉快? -好的很
- So   how was the flight? - Fuckin' great.
用@能送我去史_Du?
Will this get me to Staten Island?
_什N玩笑? 就是把你送到科特角去也行
Are you kiddin' me? This will get you to Cape Cod.
克R{斯去接生意   斯特安排v
McManus came to us with the job. Fenster got the vans.
哈肯尼提供械
Hockney supplied the hardware.
我t想k法令各人不致被
I came through with how to do it so no one got killed.
基D? 基D把整妒绿砩献钺嵋还P
But Keaton? Keaton put on the finishing touch.
稍有差e我五人⒙涞骄方手上
A little "fuck you" from the five of us to the NYPD.
看著c
Watch this.
小心
Careful.
真死
Come on   asshole!
天啊!
Holy shit!
-e  混蛋! -把放下  sN!
- Don't move   you fucker! - Drop it now   motherfucker!
把他的G掉!快G掉!
Drop the fuckin' gun! Drop it!
e他的碰任何|西
Don't fuckin' touch a fuckin' thing.
-你想要质颤N? -把那死的|西拿_
- What do you guys want? - Put your fuckin' thing away.
我是T警  蠢!
We're cops! Stupid assholes!
-小心玻璃! -e  sN!
- Watch the glass! - Don't fuckin' move   motherfucker!
-想Lw子?胖子 -]嘴!
- You want a buckshot shampoo   chubby? - Shut up!
他的
Fuck.
下午好  兄弟.把|西o我
'Afternoon   my little pork chops. Give me the shit.
-e! -把那|西o他!
- Don't move! - Give him the shit!
快把那死的|西o他!
Give him the fuckin' thing!
Give him the fuckin' shit   man!
快c!拿!
Hurry up! Come on!
-有X -]有X了
- Now the money! - There's no money.
-把X交出! -根本]有X
- Give me the money now! - There's no fuckin' money.
把Xo他!
Give him the fuckin' money!
-快!把Xo他! -把Xo我!
- Do it! Give him the money! - Give me the money!
-把Xo他! -快c!
- Give him the money! - Hurry up!
你知道我是l?
You know who the fuck I am?
你@些砘镏道我是l? 他的!
You people know who the fuck I am? Fuck!
F在知道了
We do now   jerk-off.
混蛋
Cocksucker.
等等  那算什N?
Wait a minute. What's that?
@到底算什N?
What the fuck?
天啊!
Holy shit!
走!
Go!
基D打了匿名
Keaton made an anonymous phone call.
新界cT警一起抵_F
The press was on the scene before the police were.
三日後  史道及瑞被控罪
Strausz and Rizzi were indicted three days later.
不到星期   又有50多T警亦被控罪
Within a few weeks   50 more cops went down with them.
@案子窟B很V   直到挖出了他的^X
Everybody got it right in the ass   from the chief on down.
值钠亮O了
It was beautiful.
我欠你K半
I owe you $2.50.
基D博士
Dr.Keaton.
-比我想的要多 -NE的砘锸颤Nr候到?
- There's more here than I thought. - When's the fence coming?
雷德福特不主硪我 一般都是我去找他
Redfoot never comes to see me. I always go to see him.
在加州?
In California?
是的  S伯  在加州 斯特和我--
Yes   Verbal   in California. Fenster and I--
等等  先收 你和斯特?不行
Wait   hold the fuckin' phone. You and Fenster? No.
-你想耍我? -那N派l去?
- You fuckin' kiddin' me? - So then   who's gonna go?
我一起去
We all go.
你有什N}?夥
What's your fuckin' problem   man?
我的}就是   你和斯特在加州逍b快活
My problem   is you and Fenster honeymooning in California...
…而把我甩在@e提心吊
...while the rest of us are sittin' here holding our dicks.
已完事了
The job's over.
冷oc
Cool it.
洛杉是p的好地方
LA's a good place to lay low for a while.
想要跳舞?
You wanna dance?
B
Ladies.
我提h大家忠槐
I would like to propose a toast.
敬你的
There you go.
樽阒嵌嘀\的…
To Mr.Verbal...
…"口水先生"而
...the man with the plan.
我e^班C的
We're gonna miss the flight.
e傻等了   o她留便l就行了
Don't do this. Send her a note. Something.
我f了淼眉暗
I said we'll make it.
我快要`C了
We're gonna miss the plane.
她理解的
She'll understand.
那真的很感人
That's heartwarming. Really.
我有c想哭了
I'm weepy.
到外面去等好?
You wanna wait outside?
是你想知道l生的事 我正和你f
You guys wanted to know what happened. I'm telling you.
^m吧  S伯
Come on   Verbal.
你以槲沂钦l? 你要我相信他真洗手不?
Who do you think you're talkin' to? You expect me to believe that he retired?
就榱女人?
For a woman?
胡扯  基D是在利用她
Bullshit. Keaton was using her.
-他鬯 -]e
- He loved her. - Sure.
我很y相信u粲程 不是他的主意
I'm supposed to believe that hitting the taxi service wasn't his idea.
是范斯特和克R{斯提出的 -基D做了四年的T警
- It was all Fenster and McManus. - Keaton was a cop for four years.
l比他知道的更清楚?
Who else would know better?
-他已是臭名hP -但伊迪使他全改了
- That job had his name on it. - Edie had him turned around.
我@N告V你吧
Let me tell you something.
我t解迪恩基D
I know Dean Keaton.
^去四年我一直在{查他
I've been investigating him for the past three years.
我知道@砘锸冷血的sN
The guy I know was a cold-blooded bastard.
警_除他前 已有三次被控\
IAD indicted him on three counts of murder before he was kicked off the force.
e告V我妓女也有w金子般的心
Don't sell me the hooker with a heart of gold.
你完全`了他
You got him all wrong.
是?
Do I?
迪恩基D在警r 已有七次被控罪的
Dean Keaton was under indictment seven times while he was on the force.
每次不是C人翻供
In every case   witnesses either reversed their testimony...
…就是在出庭前就被值
...or died before they could testify.
等到K於能把他入罪   K送M州立新新OzP上五年
When they finally did nail him for fraud   he spent five years in Sing Sing.
他s在e面⒘巳囚犯
He killed three prisoners inside.
然  我不能C明此事
Of course   I can't prove this...
…但我亦不能C明他]有做
...but I can't prove the best part either.
迪恩基D死^一次
Dean Keaton was dead.
你知道那故事?
Did you know that?
赡昵八在{查一宗…
He died in a fire two years ago   during an investigation into the murder...
…C人被案r葬身火海
...of a witness who was going to testify against him.
有扇艘到迪恩基D 在爆炸前M了}
Two people saw Dean Keaton walk into a warehouse he owned...just before it blew up.
他f他去z查煤馐欠漏
They said he went in to check a leaking gas main.
Y果迪恩基D就此葬身火海
It blew up and took all of Dean Keaton with it.
爆炸l生三月後   那目羧艘菜懒
Within three months of the explosion   the two witnesses   they were dead.
一是在茸
One killed himself in his car.
另一碾梯跌下而死
The other fell down an open elevator shaft.
我快_始吧
Let's get this show on the road.
我f好了不能@ F在有太多--
This is not what we discussed. There are too many--
我答他死之前我x_
I promise we'll be out before he blows his porch light.
-我中午有要_ -只能待五分
- I have a noon meeting. - Five minutes.
好  所有人要冷oc
Everyone calm down   all right?
我要你他a^鸬氖
I want you to ask this man about the shootout in the harbor.
-他f他在I-- -是毒品  我知道
- He says they were buying-- - Dope. We know.
他不知道他要I什N   但肯定不是毒品
He doesn't know what they were buying   but not dope.
-是人 -什N?
- People. - What?
他需要保C…
He needs guarantees...
-他f什N?保C? -他f他有生命危U
- What is he talking about   guarantees? - He says his life is in danger.
他到有只魔鬼在望著他
He saw the Devil. Looked him in the eye.
-我得走了 -不  再等等
- I'm on my way. - No   wait a minute.
他那他f^的…
Ask him to tell him what he told me...
…那魔鬼的事
...about the Devil.
魔鬼是l?
Who's the Devil?
P少W
Keyser Soze.
P少W?
Keyser Soze?
他在a^上⒘嗽S多人
He was in the harbor   killing many men.
他看了P少W?
He saw Keyser Soze?
-他看到了他的 -好  好
- He saw his face. - All right.
他告V她 那人的L相是怎拥
Tell him to tell her what he looks like.
形容出
Describe him.
六星期前  我接到匿名…
Six weeks ago   I get an anonymous phone call...
…f能在R甸奴餐d找到基D Y果他_在
...telling me I can find Keaton eating at Mondino's   and there he is.
由於他畏Q已死K]什N利益
Because he never profited from his alleged death...
…也因槲已找到真正的词
...and we convicted someone else of the murder we tried to pin on him...
…所以只得他走
...we had to let him go.
他畏Q死去的rg已蜷L 足以平息那宗\案的影
He was dead just long enough for the murder rap to blow over.
於是他就_始露面吃午餐了
And then he had lunch.
我δ且o所知
I don't know about that.
我不J槟阒道什N   可你f看基D死了
I don't think you do   but you say you saw Keaton die.
我在想你可能是樗掩   而他仍藏身在某
I think you're covering his ass   and he's still out there.
我J樗就是a^鸬哪会嶂魇
I think he's behind that circus at the harbor.
他利用你是因槟惚 而且J樽约菏撬的朋友
My bet is he's using you because you're stupid and think he's your friend.
你ξ艺f他已死  就他死了
You tell me he's dead   so be it.
我只想在回~s前_定他已死
I wanna be sure before I go back to New York.
他根本不是幕後主使   那是律
He wasn't behind anything. It was the lawyer.
什N律?
What lawyer?
在我在男四重唱Mr--
Back when I was in that barbershop quartet--
你以槲也恢道 你[m了地方z察官?
You don't think I know you held out on the DA?
你到底[m了什N?
What did you leave out?
我能在十分染驼业紧比
I could be on the phone to Ruby in 10 minutes.
-地方z察官已⑽一砻 -我]有
- The DA gave me immunity. - Not from me.
我K]有豁免你  混蛋
You get no immunity from me   you piece of shit.
我⑺有罪犯P在z中   每T警都感激我…
Every criminal I have put in prison   every cop that owes me a favor...
…所有犯罪的大小角色…
...every creep and scumbag that walks the street...
…都知道S伯肯特的大名…
...will know the name of Verbal Kint. You talk to me...
…你o我老交待   不然你@得的珍F豁免唷
...or that precious immunity they grant you...
…^不交到你手上
...won't be worth the paper the contract put out on your life is printed on.
有律
There was a lawyer.
叫彀脱潘够
Kobayashi.
-就是他⒘嘶D? -不是  但我肯定基D已死了
- Is he the one that killed Keaton? - No   but I'm sure Keaton is dead.
f服我相信
Convince me.
把情原原本本f出
Tell me every last detail.
我抵_洛杉去 克R{斯的NE人  雷德福特
We arrived in Los Angeles and met McManus' fence   Redfoot.
他有著不e的名   似乎是好人
He had a good reputation. Seemed like a good guy.
-可我得多t解 -好?
- Still   we should have known better. - How you doing?
-好.你呢? -也不  RR虎虎了
- Good. You? - Not bad. Can't complain.
你怎N  斯特?
How's it going   Fenster?
不需要打_吧?
Don't need to open it   right?
你一定是基D
You must be Keaton.
@是雷德福特  @是迪恩基D
Redfoot   Dean Keaton.
-陶德霍克尼  有S伯肯特. -\多多的S伯?
- Todd Hockney and Verbal Kint. - Verbal   the man with the plan.
有d趣再忠话?
You interested in more work?
-我一直在找活 -我在休假
- We're always looking for extra work. - We're on vacation.
那真可惜
That's too bad.
我有大堆的活   可惜就是找不到好手
I got a ton of work and no good people.
-要象你@般身手的 -有什N活?
- Not like you guys. - What's the job?
有牡驴怂_斯州淼闹商 叫索
There's this jeweler out of Texas named Saul.
他在市中心的酒店租了g套房
He rents a suite in some downtown hotel.
他免M槿髓b定r格 有rI  有rs不I
He does free appraisals. Sometimes he buys   sometimes he doesn't.
而言之  他手上有大PF金
The word is   he carries around a lot of cash.
我想的就是   我可以收  而你拿Fn
So I figure   I keep the merchandise   you keep the green.
-蔚暮 -安全方面如何?
- Simple. - What about security?
有保S 你完全可以搞定
A couple of bodyguards. Nothing you couldn't handle.
可以o我rg考]?
Give me time to check it out?
我聿δ闶望  兄弟
I expect nothing less from you   man.
很高d到你  M吧
Good to see you. We'll call you.
好好的在洛杉享受
Enjoy LA. Get yourself laid.
有~s朋友告V我 你JR斯伯克荷利
A friend in New York tells me that you knew Spook Hollis.
我f你曾和他一同服^刑
The way I hear it   you did time with ol' Spook.
他是好人
A good man   wasn't he?
我以前曾樗^毒
I used to run dope for him.
可惜炝
Too bad he got shivved.
是我把他值舻
I shivved him.
@事直接由我告V你 比以後e人鹘o你好
Better you hear it from me now than from somebody else later.
xx你告V我
I appreciate that.
恕我好奇…
But just out of curiosity...
@粹是公事  抑或私人}?
...was it business or personal?
烧叨际
A bit of both.
就如我f的…
Like I said...
…若你有d趣  可o我
...you give me a call if you're interested.
有}?
Is there a problem?
只忠淮
One job.
就是@
That was the deal.
只忠淮?
One job?
f的真好
That's a good one.
基D已竭M所能   但人不能改身份
Keaton fought it as best he could   but a man can't change what he is.
他可θ苏f他另一身份   但始K不能[自己
He can convince anyone he's someone else   but never himself.
克R{斯整天都在Z叨   於是我又只乇拘
It took one day with McManus nagging   and we went back to work.
於是我下了  那事全被了
I get out of my car   and the thing is wrecked.
我向另外那v的後座看去 那女人缀跞光了
I look in the backseat of the other car   and this woman's totally naked.
-我笑到快透不^ -上吧  索
- I'm laughin' so hard I can't breathe. - Get in the car   Saul.
-e  混蛋! -站著e!
- Freeze   motherfucker! - Stay right there!
There's a second one here   somewhere.
把公文箱o我 快把公文箱o我!
Gimme the case. Give me the fuckin' case!
快把公文箱o我 我v最後一次…
Give me the fuckin' case. I'm tellin' you for the last time.
快把公文箱o我!
Give me the fuckin' case!
-^! -e!
- Come on! - Don't move!
把箱子f出
Hand over the case.
o我把箱子f出
Hand over the fuckin' case.
好了  走吧!
Come on   let's go!
-快! -今天真倒楣
- Come on! - Bad day. Fuck it.
快走了!
Let's go!
混蛋
Fuck.
-就像是堆泥巴般毫or值 -真死
- Looks like a lot of china to me. - Shit.
夥  砹
Guys   come on.
-你想质颤N? -我要⒘四砘
- What are you doin'? - I'm gonna kill him.
我已按你的方式e了回   F在我的
We did it your way   now we'll do it mine.
-你要⑺? -我去和他
- You gonna kill him? - I'll deal with him.
-你最好和他好好 -]嘴
- You'd better   or I'm gonna. - Shut up.
你叫我拿@|西有什N用?
What am I supposed to do with that?
拿砦鼓酋俗影  能退止痛 我也Υ瞬恢情
Feed it to the gimp. Ease his pain. I don't know what that is.
-什N意思? -我K不知情
- What do you mean? - I don't know.
是律叫我@N做的
I got thrown this job by some lawyer.
是l?
Who?
我不知道  是英佬
I don't know. Some limey.
他也只是中g人 他不f的  我也不
He's a middleman for somebody. He doesn't say   I don't ask.
-你真是混蛋! -去死吧!
- You're fuckin' full of shit! - Fuck you.
-你才去死吧! -我f
- Fuck you. - Listen to me.
我想要他
We wanna meet him   okay?
那真巧了
That's funny.
昨晚他o我  也f想要你
He called me last night. He says he wants to meet you guys.
那好  我去他
Okay   we'll meet him.
-我o你 -好  我走
- I'll call you. - Good. Let's go.
我不想@  等等 有件事  男∽:
I don't like it. Wait a minute. One more thing   tough guy:
再玩什N花  我做了你
Any more surprises   and I'm gonna kill you.
就臀忙好?
You're such a tough guy. But do me a favor   all right?
快在我面前消失
Get the fuck off my dick.
不要!
No!
好好管教管教那小子
Put a leash on that puppy.
索被⒄媸窃愀馔噶
It's an awful shame about Saul gettin' whacked.
T警在追凶徒
Cops'll be lookin' for the guys who did it.
他t早我
Sooner or later   they're gonna come around askin' me.
祝你晚安  小姐
You have a sweet night   ladies.
去死吧
Fuck you.
-那N@律-- -彀脱潘够
- So this lawyer-- - Kobayashi.
-是雷德福特引淼? -
- Came from Redfoot. - Right.
和地方z察官f的r候楹温┝诉@段?
And why leave this out when you talked to the DA?
大l  有人找你
Dave   someone to see you.
我M世界的在找你
I've been looking all over for you.
仍在追查昨晚a^大屠⒌亩酒?
You still after that coke that took a walk out of that bloodbath yesterday?
不用查了  根本]有毒品
You can stop looking. There was no coke.
我去州立t院找了 那南滤道救上的…
I've been in LA County talking to a guy they pulled out of a drainpipe...
…昨晚疳岬存者
...yesterday after the shootout.
今早他K醒了  Kf了些事情
He came to this morning   he started talking.
他是匈牙利匪偷囊T 他A浜桶⒏廷h徒交易
He's part of a Hungarian mob. They dealt with gwats from Argentina.
他f@事c毒品交易oP
He says it was definitely not a dope deal.
-但是-- -我知道.可他f@事c毒品oP
- But there were-- - We know. But he says no on the dope.
@匈牙利人告V我 @班人翌日便要去土耳其
This Hungarian tells me they were pulling stumps for Turkey the next day.
他]rg去那批 亦]考]搬它
They had no time for that kind of product   and no means to move it.
-那X是做什N的? -他不知道
- What's the money for? - He didn't know.
除了PI人物外o人知
No one doing the deal knew except for a few key people.
他f那些人都守口如瓶
They were all very hush about it   he says.
-o那是什N  都窟B重大 -我不太明白
- Whatever it was   it was very sensitive. - I don't get it.
你到了那跛_的~s人?
You got the cripple in there from New York?
他有提到P少W]?
Did he mention Keyser Soze?
l?
Who?
原我的打_
Just bear with me here.
-l是P少W? -去死吧!
- Who's Keyser Soze? - Fuck!
我已了一半小r
We've been goin' over this for an hour and a half.
我只需要做了雷德福特 然後x_@死的地方就行
What we need to do is find Redfoot and get the hell out of here now.
我需要先思考周全
What we need to do is think.
再想想
Think back.
有人有能力…
Somebody with power...
…有人能募~s 一直追查我到@e
...somebody capable of tracking us from New York to LA.
-那我在@鹤鍪颤N? -我得等待
- What the hell are we doing here? - We're waiting.
-坐下 -不用了  我火獯笾  他┩噶
- Sit down. - No. I'm hot   and I'm fuckin' bored.
哈肯尼先生  停下
Mr.Hockney   do stay.
基D先生
Mr.Keaton.
范斯特先生  我pR他的法…
Mr.Fenster I recognize from his mug shots...
…就和克R{斯的一雍
...as well as Mr.McManus.
你一定就是肯特先生   那位值羲伯格的人
I can only assume that you are Mr.Kint   the gentleman who disposed of Saul Berg.
我的雇主致上他的感x   和一份意想不到的Y物
My employer sends his gratitude   a most unexpected benefit.
我就是彀脱潘够先生
I am Mr.Kobayashi.
我的雇主要我Х萁ㄗh
I have been asked by my employer to bring a proposal to you gentlemen.
-你想怎? -我雇主想你樗效
- What do you want? - My employer requires your services.
任罩坏靡  工作一天 但相危U
One job   one day's work. Very dangerous.
他]A你全部能活命…
He does not expect all of you to live. But those of you who do...
…但能活命的可⒛蔷徘б话偃f分了
...will have $91 million to divide between you in any way you see fit.
l是你的老?
Who's your boss?
我P少W做事
I work for Keyser Soze.
l是P少W?
Who's Keyser Soze?
你太情w化了  肯特先生
Judging by the sudden change in mood...
…我想你的合夥人也是@NJ榈
...I feel sure the rest of your associates can tell you.
我代 Soze先生向你提出建h
I come with an offer directly from Mr.Soze.
-H上是命令 -什N叫做"命令"?
- An order   actually. - What do you mean   "an order"?
1981年  你在~s巴弗洛^T劫
In 1981   you participated in the hijacking of a truck in Buffalo   New York.
上是原材料 @批材料原凫 Soze先生…
The cargo was raw steel   steel which belonged to Mr.Soze...
…本送到巴基斯坦作核反t
...and which was destined for Pakistan to be used in a nuclear reactor.
那是`反合l例的大生意
A most profitable violation of UN Regulations.
你根本不知此事  基D先生
You had no way of knowing this...
因 Soze先生承\的人
...because the fellow shipping the steel was working for Soze...
也根本毫不知情
...without his knowledge.
今年初  范斯特先生 c克R{斯先生…
Earlier this year   Mr.Fenster and Mr.McManus...
在~A克C鲵T劫了架p座C
...hijacked a two-prop cargo flight out of Newark airport.
C上d有S金和白金
The plane was carrying gold and platinum wiring also set for Pakistan.
月前  哈肯尼先生偷了…
Two months ago   Mr.Hockney stole a truck...
…途皇后^的bd械零件的
...carrying gun parts through Queens.
手零件本要由~s州政府O督N
Gun parts which were set to be destroyed by the state of New York.
但在法斯特DCr就失了
They were to be lost in a way station and rerouted to Belfast.
同拥   Soze先生利用不知情的人
Again   Mr.Soze using pawns who had no knowledge.
@游就找到了肯特先生
Which brings us to Mr.Kint.
九月前   Soze先生的…
Nine months ago   one of Mr.Soze's...
…一不算明的手下
...less than intelligent couriers was taken in a complicated confidence scam...
…被一跛子所_
...by a cripple.
他被_去了六f二千元
He was relieved of $62  000.
花了很Lrg   我才找R你
Now   it has taken us some time to find you.
我想你在~s落W後再找你
Our intention was to approach you after your apprehension in New York.
是你安排的指J^程
You set up the lineup.
是的.我未到  你是不被放
Yes. You were not to be released until I had come to see you.
看砘D先生的律菲娜琳小姐
It seems Mr.Keaton's attorney   Miss Finneran...
…做事很有效率
...was a little too effective in expediting his release.
拘留你其N各人成檎c
Holding the rest of you became a moot point.
-那雷德福特呢? -雷德福特先生也一o所知
- What about Redfoot? - Mr.Redfoot knew nothing.
Soze先生很少L久 用同一批人工作
Mr.Soze rarely works with the same people for long...
而工作的人亦不知檎l效
...and they never know who they're working for.
若]有手下  便不被出u
One cannot be betrayed if one has no people.
你槭颤N告V我?
So   why are you telling us?
因你偷了 Soze先生的|西
Because you have stolen from Mr.Soze   Mr.Fenster.
你所有人
All of you.
由於你不知道偷了他的|西 故此你尚生存
That you did not know it is the only reason you're still alive.
他X得是你欠了他 你要o他
He feels you owe him. You will repay your debt.
去他的  你去死吧 我怎知你是 Soze工作?
Fuck the debt   and fuck you. How do we know you work for Soze?
哈肯尼先生  你所f的K不切}
I don't think that is very relevant.
你五c索伯格…
All five of you are responsible for the murder of Saul Berg...
…及其保S的死有P
...and his bodyguards.
雷德福特先生可C明此事
Mr.Redfoot can testify to your involvement.
We can see to it that he will.
-你想f什N? -建h是@拥:
- What's your point? - The offer is this   gentlemen:
Soze先生一直Χ酒飞意
Mr.Soze's primary interest...
…很有d趣
...is narcotics.
他c阿根廷h的曛久
He has been competing   shall we say...with a group of Argentineans for several years.
c Soze先生抗的人 已L到了教
Competing with Mr.Soze has taken its toll.
他三天前商好了一宗…
These Argentineans are negotiating the sale...
…九千一百f元的可卡因Iu
...of $91 million in cocaine in three days time.
不用f  @P交易 重新突钏的M
Needless to say   this purchase will revitalize...the diminishing strength of their organization.
Soze先生想你制止@次Iu
Mr.Soze would like you to stop the deal.
你可等交易完成後才邮
If you choose   you may wait until after the buy.
他交易的X全凫赌
Whatever money changes hands is yours.
Soze先生想你在船上缈煽ㄒ
Mr.Soze would like you to get to the boat and destroy the cocaine onboard.
此後你就c他刹幌嗲
And then you will be free of your obligations to Mr.Soze.
o好理由 教我F在不⒛
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't kill you right now.
@是 Soze先生o你的Y物
A gift from Mr.Soze.
再  先生
Good day   gentlemen.
他知我以前的一切 由我十八q以後所作的一切
They got my whole life in here   everything I've done since I was 18.
他什N都知道
They fuckin' know everything.
甚至知道以前曾c 我一同做牢的人
Everybody I've ever worked with or did time with.
不
No.
-@事不 -我不知道
- This isn't right. - I don't know.
~s常提及 Soze的人是l?
Who's that guy who used to talk about Soze in New York?
-是布e克R林 -他g接樗做事
- Bricks Marlin. - He did jobs for him   indirect stuff.
他常f他所做的事有五倍利
He said he always made five times more money on it than the job was worth.
那人是幻想狂
This guy's a pipe dream.
彀脱潘够利用他作掩o
Kobayashi's using him for window dressing.
我不知道  @糟透了
I don't know. This is bad.
都是鬼扯.@人可能是~sT警 @根本就是圈套
It's bullshit. This guy could be LAPD. It's a fuckin' setup.
我f的 Soze是屠夫
The way I hear it   Soze's some kind of butcher.
-是Bo比的屠夫 -根本]有P少W@人!
- A peerless   psycho   fucked-up butcher. - There is no Keyser Soze!
P少W是l?
Who is Keyser Soze?
他是土耳其人 有人f他父H是德人
He's supposed to be Turkish. Some say his father was German.
人人都J樗是的
Nobody ever believed he was real.
]有人H眼^他
Nobody knew him or saw anybody that ever worked directly for him.
彀脱潘够f  任何人均可能 Sozeu命
To hear Kobayashi tell it   anybody could have worked for Soze.
o人知道 那是他害之
You never knew. That was his power.
最巧妙是其令人相信他不存在
The greatest trick the Devil ever pulled...was convincing the world he didn't exist.
那些砘锔嬖V我一故事
One story the guys told me   the story I believe
我想那是他在土耳其rl生的事
...was from his days in Turkey.
有班匈牙利人想收h徒
There was a gang of Hungarians that wanted their own mob.
他知道想碛嗔Α
They realized that to be in power   you didn't need guns...
…不用械  金X   甚至不需要手下
...or money or even numbers.
你只需做其他人不敢做的事
You just needed the will to do what the other guy wouldn't.
不久  他努力坐大 成H次於 Soze的另一大萘
After a while they come into power   and then they come after Soze.
他r萘Σ淮  只是I毒品
He was small-time then. Just running dope   they say.
一天下午  他JM他家 想要找他麻
They come to his home...in the afternoon looking for his business.
但只在家e找到他妻 於是Q定等 Soze回
They find his wife and kids in the house   and decide to wait for Soze.
Soze回家妻子被奸 孩子在哭喊
He comes home to find his wife raped and children screaming.
匈牙利人知道 Soze硬 都不敢惹他
The Hungarians knew Soze was tough   not to be trifled with.
他告V他只是想生意
They let him know they meant business.
不!
No!
他f想要他的地P   以及他所有I
They tell him they want his territory   all his business.
Sozeh家人的
Soze looks over the faces of his family.
然後向@班人以色
Then he showed these men of will what will really was.
他f他情看著家人死去…
He tells them he would rather see his family dead...
比屈辱求存好得多
...than live another day after this.
他放走最後那匈牙利人…
He lets the last Hungarian go...
等安葬了妻横   然後找@班h徒逐一
...waits until his family is in the ground   and goes after the rest of the mob.
他⒘怂的孩子   ⒘怂的妻子…
He kills their kids   he kills their wives...
…⒘怂的父母及其朋友
...he kills their parents and their friends.
掉他的居所…
He burns down the houses they live in...
…及他工作的店
...and the stores they work in.
甚至⒛切┣匪X的人…
He kills people that owe them money. And like that...
…然後就消失了
...he's gone   underground.
自此再]人^他 他成了一神
Nobody's ever seen him since. He becomes a myth.
一罪犯晚上o孩子f的故事
A spook story that criminals tell their kids at night.
"要是不   P少W就碜ツ"
"Rat on your pop   and Keyser Soze will get you."
]有人相信@事
No one ever really believes.
你相信有@人?
Do you believe in him?
基D是f:
Keaton always said:
"我不信上帝  但我怕他"
"I don't believe in God   but I'm afraid of him."
我信上帝
I believe in God.
唯一我恐值木褪P少W
And the only thing that scares me is Keyser Soze.
你Υ擞泻慰捶?
You give any weight to this?
我o你介B法院的丹曼厮固
I can introduce you to Dan Metzheiser from Justice.
他有些P於 Soze在A盛D的Y料 收集那砘锏馁Y料 缀醭闪怂的IN酆
He's got a file on Soze in DC. It's been a hobby of his for a while.
大多等艘他 中的那者
A lot of guys equate him to that reporter on The Incredible Hulk.
你^他的事?
You've heard of him?
哪?在街上?
Where? On the street?
^状  都是oP痛W的事
A few times. You know   outside stuff.
有些人g接 Soze工作   K得了些X
Someone working for a guy who worked for a guy who got money from Soze.
就是那
Shit like that.
那像是N古老的象徵   一N魔印
It could be an old badge. A hex sign.
@名字就是榱俗人躲的hh的
Keep people from fucking with you when a name meant something.
-但你已插手@事 -]e
- But you're here. - Shit   yeah.
@砘镆楹ε Soze   甚至想尼t院e逃走
This guy's trying to walk out of a hospital because he's so afraid of Soze.
我提高警X的
I'll run it up the flagpole.
我是清白的  我已f了船上的事
I came clean. I told it like it happened.
再f去那旱倪^程又有何用?
So what about how I got there?
地方z察官也曾威{我e指望特赦
It's so full of holes   the DA would've told me to forget amnesty.
你奈疑砩系玫搅讼胍的情 已了
You got what you wanted out of me. Big deal.
-楹]把@些情r向地方z察官坦白? -那N你和我f…
- That's why you never told the DA? - You tell me.
如果我向你f是尼斯湖怪雇的我   你怎N想?
If I told you the Loch Ness monster hired me   what would you say?
推翻C供  我召你作C
Turn state's evidence. We'll put you on the stand.
我已@了 你能o我_什Nl件?
I've got immunity. What can you possibly offer me?
若真有P少W其人   他碚夷愕
If there really is a Keyser Soze   he's gonna come lookin' for you.
你有]有大X?
Where's your head?
你以槭虑榫湍屈N?
Where do you think the pressure is?
o你Q呼他P少W或是什N   他知道我身在何
Keyser Soze   or whatever you call him   knows where I am right now.
他能在十分e就把我找出   然後逼你放人
He has the burner on your ass to let me go so he can scoop me up 10 minutes later.
特赦也就是你@些混蛋想出淼
Immunity was just a deal with you assholes.
若我被假  我就有了新麻
I got a new problem when I post bail.
楹巫他玩弄於股掌之g? 我能保o你
Why play into his hands? We can protect you.
多x了  大l.你f的太勇了
Thanks   Dave. Bang-up job so far. Extortion   coercion.
若我要f出不敬的也e怪我
Pardon me if I ask you to kiss my pucker.
把我s至F途末路的人 居然f要保o我?
The same fuckers that rounded us up are now bailing me out?
去你的
Fuck you.
你以槟隳艽住P少W?
You think you can catch Keyser Soze?
你以橄袼@拥娜引i待捕
You think a guy like that comes this close to getting caught...and sticks his head out?
若他真要出F  那就是榱顺掉我
If he comes up for anything   it'll be to get rid of me.
然後…
After that...
…我想你再也不到他的消息
...my guess is you'll never hear from him again.
後碓恿?
What happened next?
翌日醒  斯特已走了
We woke up the next morning and Fenster was gone.
他不想 Sozeu命
He couldn't handle the idea of slumming for Soze.
他留下字l祝我好\…
He left us a note wishing us good luck...
…拿走了我淼乃有X
...and took a chunk of the money we'd scraped together.
然後怎?
Then what?
克R{斯很怒
McManus was furious.
f要把他捉回矶缢樗的心肝
He talked about tracking him down and ripping his heart out. All sorts of shit.
那晚我接到一
That night   we got the call.
什N?
What call?
彀脱潘够f已找到了斯特
Kobayashi told us where we could find Fenster.
我快x_@
Let's get the fuck out of here.
我得先把他埋了
We gotta bury him.
用什N挖坑?
With what?
用我的手
With our hands.
神病
This is nuts.
@e全是稚
It's dry fucking sand.
等他粕砀r 一e外的jW者也能到瞥
When he rots the surfers are gonna smell him a mile away.
-o我挖 -我怎Nk?
- Dig   you fuck. - What are we gonna do?
@砘锵氚盐全至
This fuckin' guy is gonna kill us.
我不知道你的打算  拐_   但我要跑路  我]什N}
I don't know about you   peg leg   but I can run. I got no problem with that.
彀脱潘够要值裟阋]什N}
Kobayashi doesn't seem to have a problem with it either.
你就走吧   我槟阃诹硪坑
You run   and we're gonna be diggin' a hole for you.
明白?
You got that?
死的又不是我H鹤 我不欠任何人的!
This ain't my boy we're burying. I don't owe anybody!
-去你的吧 -我在一起混了五年
- So fuck you. - He was my partner for five years.
所^的X比你想像的多
We did more jobs and I saw more money than you can ever count.
你o我去死!
So fuck you!
-所以F在才要! -@不是!
- 'Cause now it's payback! - It's not payback!
@只是警告
It's precaution.
想那就去  想跑路的就跑吧 我不在乎
You want payback? You wanna run? I don't care.
我不是楣斯特@N做
I'm not doin' this for Fenster.
也不是槟@N做
I'm not doin' it for you.
我只是榱宋易约憾已
I'm doin' this for me.
我得把事情全了Y
I'm gonna finish this thing.
我不@叫彀脱潘够的s碎活下去
This Kobayashi bastard is not gonna stand on me.
斯特被⑨  ]有人逃跑?
After they killed Fenster   nobody would run?
-我想的  我知道我定能逃 -那你槭颤N不f什N?
- I wanted to. I thought we could make it. - Why didn't you say anything?
相信我  我了   但基D不同意@N做
Believe me   I tried   but Keaton wouldn't have it.
我很y穹他
It was too far-fetched for him.
基D很固  他曾是T警
Keaton was a grounded guy. An ex-cop.
T警是不接受}s的解的
To a cop   the explanation is never that complicated.
是容易受_
It's always simple.
不信街上的流言   不信幕後有黑手
There's no mystery to the street   no arch-criminal.
看到一就是二
You got a body and think his brother did it   you're probably right.
]人c基D
Nobody argued with Keaton.
人人都浜煤玫慕逃彀脱潘够
They just set their minds to whacking Kobayashi.
他上砹
They're coming up.
-收到了?他上砹 -他正下
- Did you hear me? He's coming up. - He's on his way down.
e
Don't move.
按二十  快
Press 20. Do it now.
出去
Move.
-我的答覆是"不行" - Soze先生很--
- The answer is "no." - Mr.Soze will be most--
著  混蛋 根本]有P少W@人
Listen   cocksucker   there is no Keyser Soze.
要再提@名字  我就立R⒘四
Mention his name again   I'll kill you right now.
真是奇怪   我以槟是榱⑽叶
A strange threat. I assume you've come here to kill me anyway.
我知道你找的到我…
We know that you can get to us...
…可F在你也知道了 我能找到你
...but now you know that we can get to you.
我最後o你次C去K止此事
I'm giving you one last chance to call this off.
我的雇主已Q定了
My employer has made up his mind.
-他不改主意的 -我也不
- He does not change it. - Neither do we.
你能⒐斯特   但你⒉涣宋所有人
You got Fenster   but you won't be able to get all of us.
至少在我中的某值裟阒前不
Not before one of us gets through to you.
我信你的  是真的相信
I believe you. I most sincerely do.
若你不是有能耐的人   就不被xM
You would not have been chosen were you not so suitable.
但我不能做@Q定 o你怎印
But I cannot make this decision. Whatever you threaten me with is...
…恐我都於事oa
...ludicrous in comparison to what will be done to me...
…因我必完全绦忻令
...if I do not carry out my orders in full.
想⒛愕娜司褪俏
I'm the guy that's gonna get you.
我只想你知道那c
I just wanted you to know that.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
就是我在┣  相信我
I implore you   believe me...
… Soze先生_有其人
...Mr.Soze is very real...
-…而他是很Q的人 -我等著瞧吧
- ...and very determined. - We'll see.
在你值粑抑前…
Before you do me in...
…允S我先去了Y c菲娜琳小姐的公事好?
...you will let me finish my business with Miss Finneran first   won't you?
你f什N?
What did you say?
伊迪菲娜琳
Edie Finneran.
她正在巧衔业霓k公室…
She's upstairs in my office...
…等著交涉一兑渡案
...for an extradition deposition.
她要求我H自c她@案子
I requested she be put on the case personally.
她是昨天w砺迳即的
She flew in yesterday.
]PS
No matter.
邮职
Kill away.
你在fe
You're lying.
有?
Am I?
菲娜琳小姐在洛杉期g ⑹艿胶芎玫谋Ｗo
Miss Finneran's escort while she's here in Los Angeles.
保S片刻不x其左右
Never leaves her for a moment.
我想你也高d 她的安全受到保障
I thought you'd be glad to know she's in good hands.
好好休息去吧 船在星期五到
Get some rest. The boat will be ready for you on Friday.
若你或你的朋友 有任何pe妄
If I see you or any of your friends before then...
…菲娜琳小姐受折磨而死
...Miss Finneran will be the victim of a most gruesome violation before she dies.
哈肯尼先生  你的父H…
As indeed will your father   Mr.Hockney...
…有肯特先生在 e桑那州的叔叔也如此
...and your Uncle Randall in Arizona   Mr.Kint.
我H手掉 克R{斯先生的侄子
I might only castrate Mr.McManus' nephew   David.
你都清楚了?
Do I make myself clear?
我理窍履删企w
We will take care of the two bodies downstairs.
K把那~算到范斯特先生身上
We'll add them to the cost of Mr.Fenster.
恕失陪  各位
If you'll excuse me   gentlemen.
@真是龉之的
It's a logistical nightmare.
s有十到二十人
Close quarters. 10   maybe 20 men.
我估不到船冗有多少人
There's no tellin' how many more are gonna be below deck.
要偷u那些砘?
Can we stealth these guys?
因槭嵌酒方灰   他小心防的
With all that coke   they're gonna be ready.
而且Ыo我另一}
Which brings me to sunny point Number 2.
即使我偷u成功K劫走那船 亦一o所得
Even if one of us gets through and jacks the boat   we still got nothin'.
等他收了X又如何?
What if we wait for the money?
那至少要再多值羰人
Ten more men at least.
以我看  @行不通
In my opinion   it can't be done.
lM去了都不活著出
Anyone who goes in is not comin' out alive.
-我等X到再下手 -我也是
- I'm gonna wait for the money. - Me   too.
-你有他在f? -既然M去了  就]指望全身而退
- Did you hear what he just said? - If I'm goin' in   I want a cut.
我也是
Me   too.
天下]有k不成的事
There's nothing that can't be done.
我直不敢相信   我就@N去送死
I just can't believe we're gonna walk in to certain death.
_ef~s正在下雨
The news said it's raining in New York.
他f的那是什N?
What language is that?
不知道  可能是俄Z
I don't know. Russian   I think.
好象是匈牙利Z
Hungarian?
各位  包裹已送到了
The package has arrived   gentlemen.
你浜昧?
You kids ready?
若不是停下泶鹉 就已A浜昧
I would be if I didn't have to stop and answer you.
我已渫桩
I'm ready.
克R{斯  你要在十秒雀愣
McManus   you better be set up in 10 seconds.
浜昧
I'm ready.
我要你留在@e
I want you to stay here.
我本硪掩o--
I'm supposed to cover--
如果我出不砹   上Xs快走
If we don't get out of this   take the money and go.
我不能--
I can't--
去找伊迪 告V她全部真相
Find Edie. Tell her everything that happened.
她JRS多人 她知道如何理
She knows people. She knows what to do.
如果用我的方法除不掉彀脱潘够   那N她有e的k法
If I don't get Kobayashi my way   she'll get him her way.
-可要是我-- -按我f的去做
- What if I-- - Just do what I say.
拜了
Please.
告V她….
Tell her that...
告V她我已M力了
Tell her I tried.
克R{斯  他^砹
McManus   he's on his way.
我已就位
I'm there.
?二  三  四…
One   two   three   four...
…五  六  七…
...five   six   seven...
W斯瓦德的活不好职
Oswald was a fag.
你好
Hi.
你好?
How you doin'?
有什N}?
Is there a problem?
快
Now.
王二先生有K地
"Old McDonald had a farm
伊呀  伊呀
"Ee-aye   ee-aye   O
"在那地e他⒘税嗳"
"And on that farm   he shot some guys"
明星要出隽
Elvis has left the building.
e_  e_.自己人
Hold fire. Hold fire. Vamonos!
好啊
Hello.
你楹尾惶?
Why didn't you run?
我被呆了
I froze up.
我想起了斯特被埋葬r的幼
I thought about Fenster and how he looked when we buried him.
然後我又想到基D   那r候看起硭x成功不h
Then I thought about Keaton   and it looked like he might pull it off.
有男孩在沙┥习lF一具企w
A boy found a body on the beach today.
是被人拇上下海的 ^部中了
Thrown clear of the boat. Shot twice in the head.
事物局的人去b定了他的身份
Two guys from the Bureau identified him.
-然後呢? -他叫阿D_ R克
- What else? - His name was Arturo Marquez.
是阿根廷走私犯
A petty smuggler from Argentina.
去年在~s曾因走私而被捕
He was arrested last year in New York for trafficking.
他逃往加州  但在Lu被捉回
He escapes to California. They pick him up in Long Beach.
他安排引渡他回 但又被他逃
They're setting up extradition   he escapes again.
看看@
Now   get this.
伊迪菲娜琳提出的引渡建h
Edie Finneran's brought in to advise on the proceedings.
彀脱潘够
~s鹘o了我一份 R克C供的影本
New York faxed me a copy of his testimony.
-他是告密者 -是大叛徒
- He was a rat. - A big fucking rat.
阿D_ 很害怕回到Oz
Arturo was very opposed to returning to prison.
甚至於他供出了⒔五十人
So much so   that he named close to 50 people.
猜猜最後的人名是l?
Guess who he named in the finale.
P少W
Keyser Soze
有
There's more.
我把所知一切告V你 若f重覆了就告V我
I'll tell you what I know. Stop me when this sounds familiar.
船上根本就]有毒品
There was no dope on that boat.
待著e出音
You   stay quiet.
他砹
He's here.
我知道他砹  就是他 我告V你  就是他
I know he's here. That's him. I'm telling you   that's him.
我知道他砹!
I know he's here!
-你不明白.是他 -安o
- You can't understand. That's him. - Shut up.
就是他  你到]? 我告V你  是P少W砹!
That's him. You hear me? I'm telling you   it's Keyser Soze!
-哈肯尼在哪e? -我不知道
- Where's Hockney? - I don't know.
@]毒品
There's no coke.
-什N? -你得很清楚  死的
- What? - You heard me   dumb fuck.
-根本就]有毒品! -你到底什N意思?]有毒品?
- There's no coke! - What the fuck? No coke?
我已仔搜^了每g房
I've been up and down in every fucking room.
-一定有的! -根本]有!
- There's gotta be coke! - There is nothing!
]有!
Nothing!
e跟我_玩笑了
Don't you fuck with me.
根本就]有毒品!
There is no fucking coke!
我要走了
I'm out of here.
我什N都]λf
I told them nothing.
我l誓我]有
I swear.
我什N也]f  求你了
I told them nothing. Please.
究竟是怎N回事?
What the fuck is goin' on?
@是真是太怪了
The strangest thing.
那就是你供~中所提到^的 那穿西服的瘦男人?
That's what you said. You saw a man in a suit with a slim build.
等等
Wait a minute.
你f你看了P少W?
Are you saying you saw Keyser Soze?
-先前的C供e你f不知道那男人是l -我知道船上肯定有毒品
- You said you didn't know who it was. - I know there was dope on that boat.
-e再拖延rg -我]有
- Stop stallin'. - I'm not.
-你明白我想知道什N -o我走_
- You know what I'm getting at. - Get out of my face.
我已被豁免了 不需要再受你恐
I got immunity. I don't have to take this.
你明白我想知道什N
You know what I'm getting at.
-我不知道你在f什N -f出真相!
- I don't know what you're talking about. - The truth!
告V我是l⒘嘶D
Try to tell me you saw someone kill Keaton.
我f了
I did.
你在撒e
You're lying to me.
-你知道事真相 -我不知道你在f什N
- You've known this whole time. - I don't know what you're saying.
我看基D中了  我l誓
I did see Keaton get shot. I swear to you.
你楹尾痪人?你手上有
Why didn't you help him? You had a gun.
他可是你的朋友
He was your friend.
因槲液ε
Because I was afraid.
-怕O了 -你怕什N?
- Afraid. - Afraid of what?
-怕什N-- -我知道那是P少W
- Afraid of-- - I knew it was Keyser Soze.
是P少W  他是魔鬼的化身
It was Keyser Soze   I mean   the Devil himself.
你怎N敢在魔鬼的背後_?
How do you shoot the Devil in the back?
要是射不中又如何?
What if you miss?
那f回a^的事
Let's get back to the pier.
-f^阿D_ R克? -l?]有
- Arturo Marquez. Ever hear of him? - What? No.
他是司法部的人
He was a stool pigeon for the Justice Department.
他向邦绦泄黉了份口供
He swore out a statement to federal marshals...
…f他^K能J出…
...saying that he had seen and could positively identify one...
...P少W
...Keyser Soze
@蟾嬷羞d著
It says right here in the report.
他熟知KeyserK一切I铡
He had intimate knowledge of his businesses   including...
包括\毒及\⒁酝獾氖虑
...but not exclusive to   drug trafficking and murder.
我奈绰f^他
I never heard of him.
他的手下把他出uo匈牙利h
His own people were selling him to a gang of Hungarians.
@班匈牙利人似乎 被 Soze清除Ks回土耳其
Most likely the same Hungarians that Soze all but wiped out back in Turkey.
那XK不是用碣I毒品的
The money wasn't there for dope.
@班匈牙利人收I…
The Hungarians were going to buy the one guy...
一能把P少W治罪的人
...that could incriminate Keyser Soze.
-我f了我奈绰^他 -但基D^
- I said I never heard of him. - But Keaton did.
伊迪菲娜琳是R克引渡案的
Edie Finneran was Marquez's extradition advisor.
她知道他是l  知道他掌握的Y料
She knew who he was and what he knew.
船上根本]有毒品 @只是次\⑿
There were no drugs on that boat. It was a hit.
@次自⑹降男
A suicide mission to whack out the one guy...
…目的是去值暨@ 能指CP少W的砘
...that could finger Keyser Soze.
於是 Soze派了班\去绦
So Soze put some thieves to it...
他算好了@班人一定死
...men he knew he could march into certain death.
你f Soze利用我去⑷?
You're saying Soze sent us to kill someone?
我f就是基D本人   他把你留在後面是有原因的
I'm saying Keaton did. He left you behind for a reason.
按我f的去做
Just do what I tell you.
既然o跑到何    Soze都能找到你…
If you all knew that Soze could find you anywhere...
…楹芜o你金X逃亡?
...why did he give you the money to run?
-他可以在船上就把你值 -他不想我死
- He could have used you on the boat. - He wanted me to live.
一^去的污T警
A one-time dirty cop without a loyalty in the world...
…竟然有w挽救跛子\的善心?
...finds it in his heart to save a worthless rat cripple?
@不可能  先生 你能o我理由?
No   sir. Why?
是因橐恋
Edie.
我念^到尾就不信 @改^自新的故事
I don't buy that reform story for a minute.
就算我信@c…
Even if I did...
…我也不相信他派你去保o她
...I certainly don't believe he would send you to protect her.
o我解?
So why?
因槲是朋友
Because he was my friend.
不  他不是你的朋友 基D]有任何朋友
No   he wasn't your friend. Keaton didn't have friends.
你磉@质颤N?
What are you doing here?
他留下你的命 是因樗用的到你
He saved you because he wanted it that way.
@就是他的目的
It was his will.
-基D就是P少W -不是
- Keaton was Keyser Soze. - No.
只有他才能值 哈肯尼和克R{斯@角色
A man who could wrangle the wills of men like Hockney and McManus.
只有他才能p的 在警局e安排指J
A man who could engineer a police lineup...through all his years of contacts in NYPD.
只有他才忍的⒑σ恋戏颇攘
The kind of man who could've killed Edie Finneran.
她的企w昨日在 e夕法尼州一g酒店被lF
She was found yesterday at a hotel in Pennsylvania...
…^部B中而亡
...shot twice in the head.
F在你基D有何看法?
What do you think about Keaton now?
伊迪死了?
Edie?
他利用你掩o他上船
He used all of you to get him on that boat.
@事他本硪人做不了   他必要H自下手…
He couldn't get on alone. He had to pull the trigger himself...
…以_J值袅四…
...to make sure he got his man...
…能指J他的砘
...the one man that could identify him.
全是胡f
This is all bullshit.
你fH眼看他死了
You said you saw him die.
肯定?
Or did you?
到警淼r  你想藏起
You had to hide when you heard the police cars.
你f在起火前到…
You said you heard the shot before the fire...
…可你]看他死
...but you didn't see him die.
-我t解他  他^不-- -他是在利用你
- I knew him. He would never-- - He programmed you.
他安排由你碚f整_局
He programmed you to tell us what he wanted you to.
就如你f的   他知道我不出什N
He knew we were close. You said it yourself.
保你出去的政治毫τ珊味?
Where was the political pressure to protect you from?
就是基D在幕後
It was Keaton.
-被豁免就是o你的p -但槭颤N偏偏是我?
- Immunity was your reward. - But why me?
槭颤N不挑斯特   或是克R{斯和哈肯尼?
Why not Fenster or McManus or Hockney?
槭颤N是我? 我又蠢又跛  槭颤N是我?
Why me? I'm stupid. I'm a cripple. Why me?
就因槟闶跛子
Because you're a cripple.
就因槟愫苡薮
Because you're stupid.
就因槟惚人]用
Because you're weaker than them.
要是他死了….
If he's dead...
要是你f的是真的   那N就]}了
If what you say is true   then it won't matter.
u艟是不是他的主意?
It was his idea to hit the taxi service   wasn't it?
-ξ艺f -是基D提出的
- Come on   tell me the truth. - It was all Keaton.
我一直跟著他
We followed him from the beginning.
我不知道
I didn't know.
我看到他死了
I saw him die.
我也相信他已死了
I believe he's dead. Christ.
你为一人不安全
You're not safe on your own.
你J樗是….
You think he's...
P少W?
Keyser Soze?
我不知道
I don't know.
P少W只是化名   或就如你f的  是髡f
Keyser Soze's a shield   or like you said   a spook story.
但我很t解基D   你一出去就有人等著值裟
But I know Keaton   and someone is out there pulling strings for you.
-e出去  我保o你 -我才不TD  我已自由了
- Stay here and let us protect you. - I'm not bait. I post today.
二十分前你就可以走了
You posted 20 minutes ago.
eWL想你快x_@e
Capt. Leo wants you out of here.
-除非你想翻供 -我把握C的  x了
- Unless you turn state's. - I'll take my chances.
如果有人想要值裟   那他一定要x在外面下手
If someone wants to get you   they're gonna get you out there.
若你改口供  就再也不用害怕
Turn state's evidence. You might never see trial.
也S如此
Maybe so.
可我不是叛徒
But I'm not a rat.
死的l子
Fuckin' cops.
能借用你的髡C?
Excuse me   can I use your fax machine?
在@汉名  肯特先生
You'll have to sign for these   Mr.Kint.
一K金表
One watch   gold.
金打火C
One cigarette lighter   gold.
一包  xx
One pack of cigarettes. Thank you.
我仍是一o所知
We still got nothing.
我知道了P於基D的事
I know what I wanted to know about Keaton.
那毫or值
Which is nothing.
]PS  他很快知道 我t解了多少
No matter. He'll have to know how close we came.
不管P少W存不存在
Keyser Soze or no Keyser Soze...
…只要基D活著   他就不再出F了
...if Keaton is alive   he's not comin' up again.
我去找他
I'll find him.
那是浪Mrg
Waste of time.
若是髀不平息   那就不算是髀了
A rumor's not a rumor that doesn't die.
什N?
What?
]什N
Nothing.
夥  你@赫y的
Man   you're a slob.
但|西[放的都有律
But it all has a system.
要是全[的整整RR的   就]有H和力了
It all makes sense if you look at it right. You gotta stand back from it.
要看更恐怖的地方? 到我烊ゾ椭道了
You wanna see a real horror show? See my garage.
f服我  告V我每
Convince me. Tell me every last...
我曾加入^在伊利Z州邵崎市 的一男四重唱M合…
When I was in that barbershop quartet in Skokie   Illinois...
-你到底有]有大X? -我需要先思考周全  再想想
- Where's your head? - We need to think   think back.
我肯定你已^不少餮
I'm sure you've heard tall tales.
-是布e克R林 -@事不
- Bricks Marlin. - This isn't right.
-我想你的故事 -已全f了
- I just wanna hear your story. - It's all there.
-我f的都是 -碜约又莸  名叫雷德福特
- I'm tellin' it straight. - Some guy in California called Redfoot.
-@是 Soze先生送上的Y物 -老ξ艺f
- A gift from Mr.Soze. - Talk to me.
-那雷德福特呢? -雷德福特先生K不知情
- What about Redfoot? - Mr.Redfoot knew nothing.
-利用不知情的人… -是超大胖子
- Using pawns... - A big fat guy. Like   orca fat.
有律…
There was a lawyer...
叫 彀脱潘够
Kobayashi...
我曾在瓜地R拉L^ 咖啡豆磨的新r咖啡
When I was picking beans in Guatemala we made fresh coffee.
-我知道你J樗是好人 -我知道他很好
- I know you thought he was a good man. - I know he was good.
-告V我全部的 -@事怪O了
- You tell me every last detail. - The strangest thing.
你怎N敢在魔鬼的背後_?
How do you shoot the Devil in the back?
@砘锏尼崤_很硬
This guy is protected from up on high by the Prince of...
ff你的故事  拐_佬
What's your story   pretzel man?
-有律 -什N律?
- There was a lawyer. - What lawyer?
我就是彀脱潘够
I am Mr.Kobayashi.
-彀脱潘够  彀脱潘够   -告V我所有的
- Kobayashi. Kobayashi. - Tell me every last detail.
-我P少W做事   -f服我  f服我
- I work for Keyser Soze. - Convince me. Convince me.
所有犯罪的大小角色
Every creep and scumbag that works the street...
…都知道S伯肯特的大名
...will know the name of Verbal Kint.
你^那跛子?
The cripple   did you see him?
-那跛子!他朝那e走了? -他往那去了
- The cripple! Which way did he go? - He went out that way.
我知道你知情   我知道你]f…
I know you know something. I know you're not telling...
我比你明
I'm smarter than you...
…不管你是否意   我都找到我要的答案
...and I'm gonna find out whether you like it or not.
T警是不接受}s的解的
To a cop   the explanation is never complicated.
-是那N容易受_ -真相
- It's always simple. - The truth!
根本就]什N幕手主使
There's no arch-criminal behind it all.
那人有@能力  能蛘莆铡
Somebody with power   somebody who is capable...
P少W!
Keyser Soze!
你以橄袼@拥娜引i待捕?
You think a guy like that gets this close to getting caught...and sticks his head out?
就是因槟阌薮  就因槟闶酋俗
Because you're stupid. Because you're a cripple.
F在我想知道那跛子是l?
What I wanna know is   who's the gimp?
你完全知道事真相
You've known the whole fuckin' time.
要是他硪彩且找我   我肯定基D已死了
If he comes up for anything it'll be for me. I'm sure Keaton is dead.
我的p腿]有知X  Keyser
I can't feel my legs   Keyser.
诌@行我W的 第一件事知道是什N?
First thing I learned on the job. You know what?
-就是如何辨J词 -你到那跛子了?
- How to spot a murderer. - You got the cripple in there?
-他有提到P少W? -l?
- Did he mention Keyser Soze? - Who?
那之後…
After that...
…我猜之後再不到他的消息
...my guess is you'll never hear from him again.
最巧妙乃令人相信他不存在
The greatest trick the Devil ever pulled...was convincing the world he didn't exist.
然後就象那印
And like that...
…消失的o影o
...he's gone